This is our app, TourDruid: an app to help tourists find their way around campus.
Let's say I'm a tourist.
I don't know any of these landmarks and I want to learn a little more about them.
Thankfully, I have a tour guide in my pocket. (Or a TourDruid, actually.)
So let's see how it works.
It takes you to this nice page when you open it, inviting you to start.
You click, and it presents you with a camera.
I don't really know what this building is. I'm going to go ahead and take a snapshot.
Here's the image we took.
Now we're going to send it, so that TourDruid can tell me what it is.
We see an indicator telling us it's working. And note that the majority of this time is network time.
It will present us with a list of rankings that it thinks the building is, not just one.
Hm. It seems like it thinks this is CEPSR, and seeing that little image there, I think it's right!
So, I'm going to go ahead and confirm that, and read a little more about this building.
Let's see.
Huh. So it's a research facility between Pupin and Mudd,
It has an auditorium with an 198-seat capacity, and was originally occupied by the Pegram Laboratory.
I didn't know that. Wow!
Where is it, though?
Oh, it's up there, indicated by a little red dot! That's amazing.
Let's go back, and try it again.
It seems like there's this building over there that I've never seen before.
I'm gonna go ahead and take a picture of that one, too.
That looks pretty good.
Let's go ahead and send it.
Again, the indicator's back up, and it's going to tell me what it thinks it is.
Hm, it looks like it's NoCo, and seeing that picture, that looks right!
I'm gonna click it, and here's some more information.
That guy looks happy!
Wow, this is brand new!
Amazing!
Whoa, I didn't know that about that!
So you see, all of this information would be very helpful to a tourist. No need to wait in those silly tour groups.
And where is it? Oh, there's another red dot.
This is the basic functionality of TourDruid, and we think it'll help a lot of tourists on campus enjoy themselves.
And it'll be a fun and interactive way to get along with the campus.
Thanks!